<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Risk Topics :: Safety Third</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/03-risk/index.html</link>
    <description>Please See&#xA;Risk Terminology for a review of terminology relating to risk. Risk Profile Designer for the Risk Profile Designer, to help you build a personal risk profile.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:48:25 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/03-risk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Risk Terminology</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/03-risk/risk-terminology/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:48:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/03-risk/risk-terminology/index.html</guid>
      <description>A Brief Dictionary of Risk With examples as it applies to the kink community Author’s Note!&#xA;Whether or not we are aware of it, risk evaluation is something that we all do every day of our lives. As kink enthusiast, it is even more important to be consciously aware of the risks involved in the activities we undertake. This writing, while not meant to be a comprehensive guide, will hopefully provide you with the vocabulary to talk about risk in a meaningful way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk Profile Designer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/03-risk/risk-profile-designer/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:48:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/03-risk/risk-profile-designer/index.html</guid>
      <description>Instructions Author’s Note!&#xA;This form was originally intended to be used in conjunction with my dungeon safety, and etiquette class “Safety Third!”. It is also possible to use as a standalone document for evaluating and tracking your own Risk Aware Consensual Kink (RACK).&#xA;About this form:&#xA;This is not meant to be a “Wishlist” or “Outcomes I want checklist! This is meant to serve as examples of what could happen during different types of kink scenes/play. Let me reiterate: All forms of play have some level of risk to the participants. What you accept is up to you.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>